♪♪
[ Static crackling ]
-Grandpa?
♪♪
Is that you?
It's me.
You don't recognize my voice?
♪♪
Listen -- I can only talk
for a few minutes.
♪♪
I'm in trouble.
I'm in serious trouble.
Can you help me?
I was in an accident...
...a really bad accident.
They say...They're saying
I might have to go to jail.
I know that sounds bad, Grandpa,
but it's not my fault.
You can't tell anyone
about this, okay?
You're the only person
I can trust.
I have to tell you
one more thing,
and please don't be mad.
They want money.
They want money,
or they're not letting me go.
-[ Chuckles ] That's right.
When do they need it?
-They need it right now,
Grandpa.
♪♪
This is serious.
Don't you want to help me?
You're not just going to leave
me here, are you?
-That's great.
-Please, Grandpa.
-You're scared.
-I'm so, so scared.
-[ Chuckles ]
-Will you help me?
-"I need you to help me."
-I need you to help me.
Help me!
Oh, God, help me!
Please, Grandpa.
-"I need you!"
-Help me!
-Say it. "I need you."
-I need you.
-[ Pitifully] "I need you."
-[ Chuckles ]
-Help me!
-That's great.
-Help me, help me, help me!
Help me.
[ Water dripping ]
[ Indistinct chatter ]
-Ms. Sadik...
So, you're guaranteed
to find them...
[ Indistinct chatter ]
-So, where? Where is it?
-In Aurora.
[ Indistinct chatter continues ]
-Uh, but she's just been...
-Yes.
[ Woman laughs ]
[ Indistinct chatter continues ]
-But nothing -- you know,
I wouldn't freak out just yet.
♪♪
[ Indistinct chatter continues ]
-Ms. Sadik, I appreciate you
coming on such short notice.
-Oh, it's no problem.
-Have a seat.
I have a mountain of paperwork
for you to sign.
[ Sighs ]
We've had a fair amount
of turnover lately.
It's been a challenge
finding the right match
for this patient.
He's difficult.
Um, eccentric on a good day.
-What's his condition?
-The family moved him in here
when he started hitting
on the housekeeper.
He thought she was his wife.
They thought possibly
early-onset Alzheimer's.
We're still ruling things out.
Listen -- I know you
don't have a lot of experience,
but I have a good feeling
about you.
-I'd really like
to be helpful here.
-The pool is closing
for the day.
Please return to your villas.
♪♪
[ Door opens ]
[ Door closes ]
[ Indistinct chatter ]
-I think that's the wrong size.
-Oh, I kind of like it baggy.
-Here. Why don't you try this?
Are you working days or nights?
-I'm on nights.
-Nights are really special.
You'll see.
There you go. See?
That fits perfect.
It's amazing to be needed,
isn't it?
It feels good
to mean something to somebody...
...to be absolutely necessary,
you know?
-Thank you.
-Sure.
I'll see you around.
♪♪
[ Indistinct chatter ]
[ Quacking ]
[ Birds chirping ]
♪♪
-Before we begin the test,
I want you to remember
this list of words, okay?
Face, pink, satin, box, tree.
Now I'm going to read you
a list of letters,
and you're going to tap
your head with your hand
each time you hear
the letter "A," okay?
-The letter "A."
-That's right.
"F," "B," "A," "C."
[ Birds chirping ]
"B," "A," "B."
Can you tell me
the day of the month?
-I don't know.
-And what about
the day of the week?
-I don't keep track.
-And where are we right now?
Do you know where you are?
-In a house.
Not my house. [ Inhales ]
My house didn't look like this.
It looked different.
It was better.
-And what were those words
I told you to remember?
Can you name them?
-The words?
-Yes, the five words.
Do you remember them?
-I was never good at school.
[ Lighter flicks ]
Do you want one of these?
-Don't let him scare you, Eleni.
He's just a bored, old man.
♪♪
All right.
I'm not an invalid.
-Yes, you are. Don't be stupid.
Can you get us some towels?
-Stop! Stop, stop. Stop.
Stop it.
You're getting water everywhere.
Oh, my God. Look at me.
You learn to play along.
It's easier that way.
-Hey, Mona?
[ Chuckles ] Mona?
I need you.
♪♪
-He's all yours.
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Dogs barking in distance ]
-Is that better, Mr. Callum?
-It isn't right.
-Well, tell me how you want it.
-I should be taking care of you.
-But I'm the nurse.
-That doesn't matter.
Let me take care of you.
-[ Whispering ]
♪♪
[ Laughter ]
[ Indistinct chatter ]
♪♪
-Mmm...
You want to make sure
that one arm is
firmly around their waist
like this,
so that they feel secure, and
keep their other arm real tight.
-I'm supposed to be sleeping.
-It's okay.
Tell them to put one foot
in front of the other like that.
And you really want to make sure
that they don't go too deep.
[ Laughs ]
You can't let go of them.
Tell me.
-Uh, make sure they
don't go too deep.
-Yeah.
-Don't let go.
-Yeah, exactly.
Douglas? Douglas?
You want to come in?
-I like watching you girls.
-Where were you working
before this?
-I...wasn't.
[ Indistinct chatter ]
I took some time off.
-The girls said you
got fired from your last job.
-It was just a misunderstanding.
-Did you...I mean,
you seem
to be taking to it very well.
-Oh, um, thank you.
-Yeah.
-I wasn't myself for a while,
but I like it here.
♪♪
[ Dings ]
-Water.
[ Water running ]
[ Glass clangs ]
What's your name again?
-Eleni.
That's nice. I like that.
-Thank you.
-And what do you do, Eleni, hmm?
-I'm a nurse.
-I know you're a nurse.
What do you do for fun?
-I don't know.
I don't do anything.
-You're telling me
you don't have any fun?
-I have fun helping my patients.
-Yeah. I bet you do.
-[ Exhales ]
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Chirping continues ]
Sorry.
I accidentally fell asleep.
-Hey. Good morning.
-You're supposed
to be sleeping.
-I'm gonna make a call.
-In the middle of the night?
-It's business.
-What business?
-Can you repeat after me?
-Who are you calling?
-Just repeat after me. Okay?
"Grandpa, I can only talk
for a few minutes."
-I don't understand.
-Just do it.
-Grandpa, I can only talk
for a few minutes.
-[ Whispering ] Do you hear him?
[ Normal voice ] "I was in
an accident. I hurt someone.
They say I might
have to go to jail."
-I was in an accident.
I hurt someone.
-[ Whispering ] "They say..."
-They say I might
have to go to jail.
-"Wait by the phone.
My lawyer's gonna call
you right now, okay?"
-Wait by the phone.
My lawyer is going to call
you right now, okay?
-"I love you."
-I love you.
[ Hangs up receiver ]
-[ Chuckles ]
-Who was that?
-Oh, hello.
Yes, uh, Mr. Goldberg.
Hello. Uh, my name is Richard.
I'm the attorney assigned
to your relative's case.
Now, as Sarah informed you, uh,
she was involved in an accident.
She has a fractured nose,
but other than that,
she's uninjured.
The woman in the other vehicle,
however, is in the hospital.
Unfortunately, Sarah's
blood alcohol content was 0.10.
That is well above
the legal limit.
Oh -- pfft! --
she drank quite a bit.
We were all impressed.
Now listen.
Here's what's going to happen.
In the morning,
we're going to see a judge
for what is called
an arraignment hearing.
Now, if Sarah gets charged with
reckless endangerment and a DUI,
she could be required to remain
in custody for up to 30 days.
Now, luckily for you,
I spoke to the judge in chambers
because Miss Sarah here
has a clean, clean record.
Mm-hmm. She's a good girl.
I'm sure you agree that jail is
no place for a girl like Sarah.
Now, if we can raise
the $10,000 bond,
they'll dismiss the
reckless-endangerment charge,
and she could go home tonight.
I know.
No, it is difficult
to raise that kind of money.
How about tomorrow night?
Tomorrow night? Okay.
Now, I have to ask you.
Don't mention this to anyone.
The judge has placed
a gag order on this case
because of the narcotics
found in the vehicle
at the time of arrest.
I know.
No, that doesn't sound
like Sarah,
but people can surprise you,
sir.
Yeah. Right in the mailbox.
Easy as that.
Mm-hmm. Okay.
I'm gonna hang up now.
Um, bye-bye.
[ Laughing ] There's no need
to thank me, sir.
I'm just doing my job.
Okay. Bye now.
[ Hangs up receiver ]
You're a natural.
-What was that?
[ Exhaling sharply ]
Have you looked at yourself?
You're too old.
You make me sick.
Do you like that?
Tell me what you like.
I-I want you to feel good.
-[ Laughs ]
-Did I do something wrong?
-[ Sighs, chuckles ]
[ Insects chirping ]
You're looking for a pogo stick,
I'm really not your guy.
[ Lighter flicks ]
♪♪
-Everything
I did before today wasn't me.
It was somebody else.
-Okay.
-And the person I was,
I don't know her.
-You're not her. You're you.
-We're two different people,
and I don't want to talk
about her anymore.
-We don't have to talk
about her.
Are you crying?
-I shouldn't have done it.
-[ Laughs ]
-I don't know
why you're laughing.
You wouldn't be
if you were in my situation.
-Don't cry. You helped him.
-I did.
-Mm-hmm.
Before last night,
that old man sat alone
in his house all day long.
And for what?
-He sounded so scared.
-He was numb to life
before today.
You gave him purpose.
You helped him.
-I helped him.
-Of course you did.
You gave him something
to live for.
-I didn't realize.
[ Insects chirping ]
♪♪
-How'd you sleep, honey?
-Hours are hard.
We're getting used to it.
♪♪
-[ Sighs ]
-Could I have one?
♪♪
-No.
But you can have one of Mona's.
♪♪
[ Car departing ]
[ Tires screeching ]
♪♪
-How'd you get that car,
Douglas?
-Who's asking?
-Here's the deal.
You can't buy a car
if you don't have money.
And that's what
I don't understand.
♪♪
That's it, Dougie.
Yeah, it's the end of the rope.
No more money, no more handouts.
-[ Sarcastically ] Oh, no.
[ Laughs ]
[ Coughing ]
-Maybe you can find a job
or something. I don't know.
-Come on, Nance!
Do you see where we are?
I'm demented.
-Please, Mrs. Callum.
You know how he is.
He needs you.
-Yeah. I know.
[ Footsteps departing ]
[ Insects chirping ]
-You know I don't just
hang out here for fun, right?
-I don't know.
She's filthy rich.
-You really fucked this up,
didn't you?
-[ Inhales deeply, exhales ]
♪♪
[ Insects chirping ]
-Grandpa...I only have
a few minutes to talk.
-That's right.
-I was in an accident.
I hurt someone.
They say I might
have to go to jail.
[ Douglas laughs ]
Ooh! I don't have time
for questions.
Please don't be mad, Grandpa.
You're the only one I can trust.
You can't tell anyone
about this, okay?
-Ask for the money.
-They want money.
They want money,
or they're not letting me go.
Wait by the phone.
My lawyer's gonna call
you right back, okay?
[ Blows kiss ] I love you.
[ Hangs up receiver ]
[ Laughter ]
-What is so funny?
This is a serious problem
we're dealing with.
I don't want it leaving
this room, all right?
-The callers target men
over the age of 65
in various states
of cognitive decline.
And they've taken
a quarter-million dollars
in this mile radius.
Whether it's an amateur behind
this or an organized group,
we don't know yet.
-Ladies, call us
if you know something.
All right?
-Thank you.
Okay, everybody,
get back to work.
♪♪
[ Car engine humming ]
-What about him?
-Oh, we tried Mr. Linker.
He's too with it. Remember?
♪♪
How about that one?
-Oh, yeah.
I think his family's
pretty loaded.
They got a lot
of nice cars parked out front
from time to time.
What do you think, Mona?
-I don't know.
-Oh, come on, Mona!
I know you've got
all these guys lined up
in that head of yours...huh?
-Maybe I'm demented, too.
-[ Laughs ]
♪♪
Let's go, Eleni.
[ Gulls cawing ]
♪♪
-You're behind
on your payments, Mr. Callum.
Are you aware of that?
-You should talk to Nancy
about that.
-Mrs. Callum is no longer
the guarantor on your account.
-Did she say that?
-Mm.
That's what I'm seeing here.
-Yeah, well,
I gotta talk to her.
-So, she is handling
your account?
-Yeah, she is.
I just gotta talk to her.
-Okay. Good.
♪♪
Do you remember the test
you took over the summer?
-What test?
-"Face, pink, satin, box, tree."
-Mona, come over here.
Mona, what are you doing?
-Doesn't ring a bell.
-Well, out of 30 points,
you scored 12.
-[ Laughs ]
-What? Hey! Could be worse.
What do you think, girls?
♪♪
-What's wrong with her?
-She's just tired.
-Mr. Callum, if you are as sick
as this test would indicate,
I need to change things up
with your care.
-Okay.
Would... more help?
More girls?
-Doug...Douglas.
-What's the plan?
-Mona, may I speak with you
for a minute in the other room?
-Douglas,
are we going to be okay?
-Yeah. We're okay, baby girl.
[ Birds chirping ]
♪♪
[ Door opens ]
♪ It truly would be grand
if you would understand ♪
♪ I'm gonna telephone
my baby ♪
♪ Ask her to come on home ♪
♪ Baby, won't you please
come home? ♪
♪ 'Cause your daddy's
all alone ♪
Michelle, come over here.
-Me?
-Yeah, you. I need you.
-What do you need?
-[ Laughs ]
Michelle, what a gorgeous name.
-Thank you.
-No one is called Michelle
anymore.
What do you do for fun,
Michelle?
-[ Laughing ]
Well, I don't know.
-What do you like?
-I don't know.
-Come on! You like something!
What is it? You like something.
Do I know you? [ Laughs ]
I don't know you. [ Chuckles ]
I know you.
What do you like to do for fun?
-I don't know.
-You don't know?
-No! I--
-Well, I think we have
a serious problem.
-There's no problem.
-No, we have a serious problem.
The girls aren't having any fun!
-What do you like
to do for fun?
-Me? Oof. I'm old.
Nobody cares if I have fun.
But you girls...
You girls...[ Laughs ]
People want to know!
Ah! The world is watching.
People want to know.
-I feel sick.
-[ Laughs ]
-I feel really sick.
-Michelle, you know
what's great about these things?
-What?
-I'm going to feel
fantastic tomorrow.
You know how many vitamins
is in this stuff?
-A lot!
-It's like, it's like
three...six...
...nine.
-[ Laughs ]
-The room is spinning.
-Oh, sit down, Molly!
-My stomach hurts.
I want to go to bed.
-Honey.
[ Laughing ] My poor baby.
-Twelve. [ Laughs ]
-[ Laughs ]
-Oh!
-She's sick.
Does anybody have a bag?
-[ Laughs ] Uh...ah!
Uh, bag standing by.
-Wait, wait, wait.
She can have mine.
-Bag coming up. [ Laughs ]
I am at your service. [ Sighs ]
[ "Baby, Won't You Please Come
Home?" by Bessie Smith plays
in background ]
Oh, my.
You're tall.
[ Both laugh ]
Oh, there we go.
Aah.
-♪ Make you understand ♪
-Nurse! [ Laughs ]
Nurse. [ Laughs ]
Nurse, prepare the tape.
-♪ Ask him, won't you... ♪
-Oh, here we go.
-♪ 'Cause when you're gone,
I'm worried... ♪
-Oh, you've got lovely veins.
[ Both chuckle ]
-♪ Baby, won't you please
come home? ♪
-Here we go.
-♪ Baby, won't you please
come home? ♪
-Ahh.
-Yes? Yes?
Tape, please. Ah.
You've done this before.
-♪ ...to call your name ♪
♪ When you left, you broke... ♪
-There you go.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
-♪ That will never
make us part ♪
-[ Laughs ]
Eh! Uh! Gross. [ Laughs ]
Michelle? Come on. Come on.
I want you to have fun.
-I'm having fun.
-I want you to have a good time.
-I'm having--
-Hop aboard! Let's go.
-No-o-o-o!
-Come on!
-No, stop! No.
-Come get it.
♪ Baby,
won't you please come home? ♪
-Oh, no! Aah!
♪ 'Cause your daddy's
all alone ♪
-[ Laughing ] Oh, stop!
[ Both laugh ]
-♪ I have tried ♪
I've got to get down!
I'm so tired.
-No, no!
Not allowed.
-[ Laughs ]
-[ Laughs ] Not allowed!
-Aw!
-Not until we do the Hop.
♪ Baby, won't you please
come home? ♪
-I don't wanna...
-I see you.
I know what you...
Come on.
Up!
♪ And, baby, I feel so lonely ♪
♪ When I call you
on the telephone ♪
♪ I have tried ♪
Come--
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, come -- girls, no sleeping.
No sleeping in this house.
Come on. Get up, get up.
Let's go.
A little dance.
No--
-No!
I know you love this song.
♪ Baby... ♪ [ Laughs ]
♪ I'm gonna telephone my baby ♪
Come on, girls!
Somebody's gotta take care
of you girls.
Make sure you're having fun,
having a good time.
What? No sleeping,
no sleeping in this house.
Girls! Come on.
No, no, no, no, no.
-You know, I knew this guy who
didn't sleep for a whole year.
-What happened to him?
-Please. No --
-He died.
-Girls,
we're supposed to be having fun.
This is a party.
Everyone up! Get up!
What are you doing?
-Do you think I'm gonna die?
-Come on. Up.
-No, I don't think so.
-Up!
-He had a...
He had a rare genetic disease.
-Please, girls.
-Sleep disease.
-♪ ...move May the first ♪
♪ Baby,
won't you please come home? ♪
♪ I need money ♪
♪ Baby, won't you please
come home? ♪
[ Bottles clanging ]
-Are you okay?
-The girls don't
want to have fun, I guess.
-I want to have fun.
-What happened?!
We used to have food in here.
-We haven't been to the store
in a while.
-I thought it would be fun
to have fun, to have a party.
-They're tired.
So what?
-I should be tired.
-Oh, let's make a call.
-I don't want to.
-Why not?
-Because I'm hungry.
-I want to make a call.
-Get off of me!
[ Bottles clink ]
[ Bottles clinking ]
I didn't mean that.
You know that, right?
-Get off of me!
-Stop it!
-You're too old.
-I know.
-You make me sick.
-Yeah, I know.
Okay, baby girl,
let's see you do a call.
-I don't want to anymore.
-I want you to.
-Go away!
-No.
You're in trouble.
-No, I'm not.
-Oh, yes, you are.
-What kind of trouble?
-You're in jail.
-It's so cold in jail...
...cold and unforgiving.
-Yeah.
Yeah, it is.
...132, baby.
[ Ringing ]
[ Woman talking on TV ]
[ Ringing continues ]
-What's wrong?
-I had to take two weeks
on the night shift
at the emergency clinic.
-Hello?
-[ High-pitched voice ]
Grandpa, is that you?
-No.
Say it like yourself. Okay?
-[ Normal voice ] Grandpa,
is that you?
It's me.
You don't recognize my voice?
I'm in big trouble.
Will you help me?
I was in an accident.
-That's good.
-I hurt someone.
-That's right. Jail.
-They say
I might have to go to jail.
Please, Grandpa?
[ Voice breaking ]
It's not my fault.
You know that, right?
You forgive me?
They've tied
the handcuffs so tight.
My hands are tied.
My feet are tied.
And it hurts.
It hurts really, really bad.
-So mean.
-And they're so mean to me.
The guards are so mean.
And it's so cold.
It's so cold.
Help me.
-Please.
-Help me. Please help me.
Help me!
-"I need you."
-Help me. I need you.
I need you.
[ Crying ] I need you.
Help me.
Help me, help me, help me.
Please help me.
Please help me! Please help me!
-Oh, oh. Oh, gosh.
[ Stammering ]
There --
there's something wrong.
[ Stammering continues ]
-Hello?
Hey. Hello? Are you okay?
♪♪
-Hello? Hey! Hey.
Are you okay?
Hello?
Hey. Are you okay? Hello?
♪♪
Oh, fuck.
[ Hangs up receiver ]
Aw, fuck.
I think he's dead.
-No, he's not.
-What the fuck did you do?
-It was...
It was just a phone call.
-Ugh!
[ Motor humming ]
♪♪
[ Ambulance humming ]
[ Water dripping ]
♪♪
-Is the water too hot?
-I want to get out.
-Okay.
I'll get you a towel.
♪♪
[ Water running ]
-Mona?
[ Water stops ]
-You know Mona isn't here.
-What?
-Mona isn't here.
-I know.
[ Water splashes ]
[ Muffled chatter ]
Oh, you're a good dancer.
-[ Laughs ]
-I like a good dancer.
-So, what did
you talk to Michelle about?
Douglas?
[ Microwave humming ]
[ Microwave dings ]
[ Footsteps approaching ]
Douglas?
-Huh?
-Did you and Michelle talk?
-Yeah. We talked.
What else am I supposed to do
with a girl for 12 hours?
-Well, what did you guys
talk about?
-I don't know.
Huh.
We didn't talk about anything.
[ Drawer opens ]
-Are you not hungry?
[ Money ruffling ]
I'm not throwing this away
again.
-What?
[ Water running ]
[ Water stops ]
[ Drawer closes ]
[ Footsteps approaching ]
What?
-Nothing.
-[ Sighs ] Come on.
-You're in trouble.
-No, I'm not.
Do you think I'm old?
I don't want you
to think I'm old.
-I don't care that you're old.
-I'm always surprised
when I see myself.
It doesn't match what I have
in my head.
-I like how you look.
-Yeah.
You should have seen me before.
-Yeah, I've seen photos.
I don't like it.
-You don't like it?
What, are you crazy?
-I like you better now.
You smell.
-I know.
-Can we do it again?
-It's too soon.
-Please?
-When do you think?
-I don't know.
[ Sighs ]
Come on. Don't be like that.
-Be like what?
Hey!
-Jesus! What?
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
I just need to make sure.
[ Money ruffling ]
[ Douglas counting quietly ]
-[ Sighs ]
[ Money shuffling continues ]
[ Eleni picks up
phone receiver ]
-[ Douglas mumbles to self ]
-Hello?
Grandpa, hi.
Yeah. It's me.
Listen, um...I'm in trouble.
Can you help me?
-Hey!
What the fuck are you doing?
Get--
-Yeah, please.
I really need help.
-What did I just say?
[ Douglas slams receiver ]
Huh?! What'd I just say to you?
-It's too soon.
[ Footsteps departing ]
[ Machine beeping ]
[ Beeping continues ]
[ Rapid beeping ]
[ Motor humming ]
-Do you know where you are?
Mr. Callum, take a seat.
-Who took them?
-Mr. Callum...
-Where are you trying
to take me?
-I'm not trying
to take you anywhere.
We're just having
a conversation.
-I...
-Please, sit still.
-[ Groans ]
-Michelle,
would you take his vitals?
-Is that the doctor?
-When did these symptoms begin?
-Pretty much since I started.
-Mr. Callum?
-Mm?
-Do you know where you are?
-I know where I am.
-Oh, good.
Where are you?
-My mom is supposed
to pick me up in a little while.
Does she know where I am?
-Yes, she knows.
-She knows where I am?
-Yes.
-OxSat normal, BP high.
-Okay, call the paramedics,
would you?
-Do you have...
do you have a cigarette?
-No, I don't.
-Have you seen my cigarettes?
-I haven't,
but I'm sure they're fine.
We need to transfer
Mr. Callum to assisted living.
-The big house?
-Oh, it's fine. It's fine.
It's really lovely there.
-Big.
-Mr. Callum...
-Where are my cig--
-Mr. Callum?
-Where are...
-Douglas, stop that right now!
-Mr. Callum.
-Mm-hmm?
-If you wouldn't mind
just sitting down for a minute?
[ Clock chiming ]
Please.
-Over here.
-Yes. Come on in.
-Hey, Doc.
-Mr. Callum?
-Yeah?
-Hey, Mr. Callum.
-Oh. Hey, Ralph.
-How you doing?
Did you lose something?
-Uh, yeah. It's over here.
-We gonna make it easy,
or we gotta get you a cocktail,
Mr. Callum?
-Oh, take it easy.
-[ Sighs ]
Where do you want it,
Mr. Callum?
-I want it in the butt.
-Okay.
You don't have to beg.
In...
-[ Groans ]
-...and out.
-Oh, oh!
-He's good.
Okay.
-Okay.
-All right, there we go,
big guy.
All right.
-Thank you.
-Ready?
One, two, three...
[ Douglas groans ]
-Okay.
-There you go.
-There we go.
-Got that?
-Yeah.
-[ Chuckles ] It's okay.
We've got you.
-One, two, three...
[ Stretcher clatters ]
♪♪
[ Monitor beeping ]
-Open wide.
There you go.
[ Footsteps approaching ]
-I'll take it from here.
[ Beeping continues ]
You're in bad shape.
-Aren't you bored?
-Oh...
Nah, I'm on the clock.
-Life's...
life's not all about work.
[ Beeping continues ]
-This doesn't feel like work.
-Yeah, right.
-Feels good.
-I don't believe you.
[ Beeping continues ]
-I like taking care of you.
-I should have invited you
to the party.
-You need to get some rest.
[ Beeping continues ]
[ Footsteps departing ]
♪♪
-[ Coughing ]
-She said he was just lying
there like a vegetable.
-It's so sad.
-It's like one day
you're completely yourself,
and the next
you're fucking dead.
♪♪
-Okay.
-[ Whispering ] Douglas?
♪♪
Douglas?
Douglas, it's me.
♪♪
It's me.
-That...that tickles.
-[ Chuckles ]
I really want to do one
of the calls.
-Eleni?
-Yeah. It's me.
-Um...
-I really want to.
You have such soft skin.
Like a woman.
Like a baby.
Why do you have such soft skin?
You smell good.
You smell really good.
-Eleni? Eleni?
-Can you hold me?
[ High-pitched voice ]
Mr. Lawyer...
should we call my grandpa?
I'd really like
to get out of jail.
[ Both laugh ]
What's a girl like me
going to do in jail?
-What...
what is that funny voice?
-I'm not trying to be funny.
-It's a funny voice.
-[ Normal voice ]
Tie my hands up.
-Ow. Ow!
-Sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
What did she do to you?
Douglas? Douglas, look at me.
Look at me.
Look at me. What are you doing?
What are you doing?
[ Insects chirping ]
♪♪
[ Water dripping ]
[ Vehicles passing ]
♪♪
-How many people you are?
-Just one.
-Just one? Okay.
You pay by cash or by card?
-Cash.
-Thank you.
It's, uh, $75, ma'am.
♪♪
[ Wheelchair rumbling ]
[ Beeps ]
-Douglas, wake up.
-I feel really bad.
-Shh.
You're just coming down
from the sedatives.
[ Woman groaning ]
-Oh.
Another...beautiful girl.
[ Groaning continues ]
Are we having a party?
-I don't want to pretend
anymore.
I want to do it for real.
-[ Laughs ]
Uh, you're wild.
You're completely wild.
-Do you like it?
-Uh, you know I love
when girls are doing things,
having fun.
[ Groaning continues ]
[ Muffled yelling ]
[ Muffled yelling continues ]
-What did you say?
Michelle?
It's okay. No. No, no.
It's okay.
I promise. I promise. I promise.
We're just doing this
for Douglas, okay?
Don't worry. Don't worry.
It's okay.
We're just gonna help him, okay?
We're just doing this to help.
-[ Crying ] Douglas, please!
Help, please!
I think she's insane. I think...
I think she's clinically insane!
-Would you stop yelling?
-Douglas, can you hear me?!
-[ Laughing ] Yeah.
Yeah, I can hear you.
-You know, I was worried
he liked you more than me.
I hate feeling jealous.
I really hate that feeling.
-Douglas, please!
[ Crying ] Please, please.
-Oh, quiet down.
I'm making a call.
[ Ringing ]
-Hello?
-"Grandpa, I can only talk
for a few minutes."
Say it.
-Grandpa...I can only talk
for a few minutes.
-"I've been kidnapped.
They have me all tied up.
My hands are tied.
My feet are tied.
My skin is popping out
between these knots."
-I've been kidnapped.
They have me all tied up.
-Oh.
-My hands are tied.
My feet are tied.
My skin is popping up
between these knots.
-Tell him we want money...cash.
-They want money.
-Tell him we want money,
or we're not letting you go.
-Please...help me.
I think they're gonna kill me.
-What'd he say?
-Um..."How much?"
-How much do you think?
-Uh...I don't know. Ten grand.
-Oh, it feels a little low.
Um, how about $100,000?
-$100,000.
He says yeah.
-What do you think?
Do you think that's a good deal?
-It's a good deal, pumpkin.
-You think?
You're acting kind of weird.
-Yeah. Yeah, no, I just...
I just need some medicine.
-Tell him we'll take it.
-They'll take it.
[ Vehicles passing
in background ]
[ Hangs up receiver ]
-Did we get the money?
-Yes, that's what he said.
-That was so good, Michelle.
You were amazing.
Just amazing.
That felt so good, right?
Huh?
That felt good, right?
That felt right?
-That's great, baby girl.
[ Kissing ]
-Is this a new game?
Douglas?
What are you doing?
Douglas, what's wrong?
-What are you do...
What-- what are you...
What are you do...
[ Muffled ] What are you...
What are you...
[ Muffled yelling ]
[ Muffled yelling continues ]
[ Yelling stops ]
-[ Breathing heavily ]
♪♪
[ Rattling in background ]
[ Rattling intensifies ]
[ Indistinct radio chatter ]
♪♪
-Hi, sweetheart.
-Sir, do you know
where you are right now?
-I know where I am.
-Where are you?
-Can I see your wrist?
-Tell me what day it is?
-"Face...pink...satin...box...
tree."
-Hey, uh, Detective?
You're gonna want to come here.
-Don't worry.
He cannot hurt you anymore.
We are going to take
good care of you now.
-What's up?
Did he confess?
-Nope.
He's talking nonsense, sir.
Random string of words,
mumbo jumbo.
♪♪